#### SEAN CONWAY

2904 Runnymede Way | Lexington, KY 40503 spconway.gis@gmail.com github.com/spconwavgis linkedin.com/in/conwaysp

#### SUMMARY

I am a graduate of the University of Kentucky with a BA in geography with an emphasis in GIS. I have worked on research including the accessibility of oral pathologists to patients and analysis of geographic distribution of squamous cell carcinoma cases in Kentucky. Also, I independently researched low cost georeferenced data logging technology based around the Arduino platform attached to unmanned aerial systems which has culminated in a research paper evaluating the efficacy of such data gathering techniques that has been submitted for publication to the Annals of the Association of American Geographers.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### UNIVERSITY OF **KENTUCKY**

2010 - 2014

## Lexington, KY

#### **BACHELOR OF ARTS**

Graduated magna cum laude with a BA in Geography, concentrating in GIS / Spatial Analysis.

Received Gyula Pauer Award for Cartographic Excellence 2014.

Member Gamma Theta Upsilon (Geographic Honor Society).

#### SKILLS

#### KNOWLEDGE BASE

•	Esri	/	ArcGIS

- GIS Modeling
- Microsoft Office

• C++

- ERDAS Imagine
- Adobe Creative Suite

- Python
- MySQL
- Global Mapper

- OrthoVista
- Q GIS
- Geomedia / OrthoPro

- XPro
- Microstation

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### QUANTUM SPATIAL

#### ORTHOIMAGERY TECHNICAL EXPERT

Lexington, KY 06 / 2015 - Present Accomplishments:

- Developed ArcGIS orthoimagery workflow upon migration from Microstation. Wrote several scripts and models in Python for Arc to improve efficiency and automate orthoimagery workflow processing.
- Introduced automation to Microstation, ESRI and OrthoVista orthophoto processing that decreased time to end product.
- Continually exploring new cartographic methods to add to available options of deliverable products.

Duties for Quantum Spatial include:

Assist Project Managers and manage technicians in production workflow of orthoimagery. Oversee large scale image acquisition and production from raw imagery ingest to delivery of final tiled product to client.

Continually exploring ways to improve GIS workflows to provide quality deliverables within reasonable time-frames.

Training new-hires in orthoimagery workflow.

Planning all levels of production for orthoimagery projects using ArcGIS. Analysis and QC/QA of LiDAR and orthoimagery data. Cost estimation of orthoimagery projects. Correction of LiDAR data using MicroStation and correction of orthoimagery in Photoshop. Orthoimagery production accomplished using XPro, OrthoVista, OrthoPro, MicroStation and ArcGIS.

#### UK ORAL PATHOLOGY LAB

### Accomplishments:

Lexington, KY 05 / 2007 – 5 / 2015

Consistently above average performance reviews.

ACCT. CLERK / MEDICAL TRANSCRIPTION

- Produced a map and statistics poster used in presentation to obtain more laboratory space and funding.
- I also produced time-saving Python and C++ scripts and programs to greatly speed up tedious tasks and visualize data.

Duties for Oral Pathology included: transcription of pathology reports utilizing Dictaphone devices, filing insurance claims, maintaining patient database information, customer service, processing customer and insurance payments and data entry.

#### DR. J. SCOTT LITTLETON, MD

04 / 2005 - 04 / 2007

#### OFFICE MANAGER

Accomplishments:
Bowling Green, KY

- Designed two programs in C++ and a multi-layer database in MS Access that are now commonly used in the office to streamline information output and billing processes.
- Making connections with some of the great kids than came to see Bowling Green's best child psychiatrist.

Duties for Dr. Littleton included: basic secretarial duties, data entry, patient relations, creating and generating forms and documents, filing and maintaining the office.

# UNITED STATES POSTAL SERVICE

#### DATA ENCODING OPERATOR

Bowling Green, KY 07 / 2002 – 03 / 2005 Duties with the Postal Service included: routing flat rate mail via encoding terminals using USPS shorthand.

#### AFNI S

#### SUPERVISOR

Bowling Green, KY 07 / 2000 – 07 / 2002

Accomplishments:

- I designed a MS Access database that utilized Visual Basic scripting and MS Outlook integration to automate common cellular phone software change requests.
- Managed a team of employees who consistently performed well above average.

Duties at Afni include: managing a team of 15+, customer service, data entry, creating and generating documents and forms, dealing with irate or escalated calls, and ensuring quality performance from my representatives.